New Himuka lied to us.
뉴히무카가 우리를 속였다
Seto, you know this better than anyone.
세토 넌 잘 알잖아
What are you talking about?
그게 대체 무슨 소리야?
I know you took part in horrible experiments.
네가 위험한 연구에 참여했다는 거 알고 있어
Experiments? Explain yourself!
연구라니, 대체 뭐라고 지껄이는 거야
Gemma, we are out of time.
겜마, 시간 없어
What's going on now?
이게 다 뭐야?
We must fight for our lives.
어쩔 수 없이 싸워야겠네
It's best that I retreat now.
난 지금이라도 빠져야겠어
Everyone, calm down.
다들 진정하라고
-Are you all right, Kasane? -I'm fine.
-카사네, 괜찮아? -응…
What is going on?
이게 다 무슨 일이야?
Our comrades are killing each other.
왜 같은 편끼리 물고 뜯는 건데
Nagi!
나기
Yuito, we always trained together.
유이토, 우리는 항상 같이 연습했었지
That was why we almost didn't make it to the enlistment ceremony.
그래서 입영식 날도 지각할 뻔했었고
Kasane, would you like to join us?
이번에는 카사네랑 함께 하는 거야?
Nagi...
나기…
SCARLET NEXUS
"스칼렛넥서"
♪A crime in reality♪
현실의 Crimｅ
♪For Heaven's sake♪
For Heaven`s sake
♪Accepts any fake♪
거짓을 받아들여
♪And disappears piling the eternity in fantasy♪
영원한 환상은 점점 사라져가
♪Won't take it at all, I get sick♪
결코 완벽하지 않아 I get sick
♪A girl looking back♪
뒤돌아 걸어오는 소녀는
♪Casts the miracle into the instant world♪
순간 이 세상에 기적을 남겨
♪Did you lie♪
Did you lie
♪Spit the venom♪
Spit the venom
♪I know why♪
I know why
♪I've found a game of ecstasy♪
최고의 게임을 찾았어
♪Red Criminal gets life♪
Red Criminal gets life
♪I've never been in love♪
I`ve never been in love
♪Don’t know when I started getting sick of this world♪
난 언제부터 이런 세상이 질렸던 걸까
♪We will fly♪
We will fly
♪Someday I won't be crying♪
Someday I won`t be crying
♪I've been sacrificing myself not to hurt anybody♪
더는 해치고 싶지 않기에 나를 희생해
RED STRINGS
(레드 스트링스)
Nagi, what are you talking about?
나기, 그게 무슨 말이야?
Are you one of Major General Karen's men?
너도 카렌 연대장과 한패야?
Kasane, don't disappoint me.
카사네, 나 실망시키지 마
I have no idea what the Major General's plan it.
연대장이 뭘 하려는 건지 모르겠지만
But I will never betray my friends.
난 모두를 배신하지는 않아
Brother...
오빠는…
You never change.
항상 이런 식이야
You never tell me anything.
아무것도 얘기 안 해주지
Do you really think so little of me?
내가 무력해서 그러는 거야?
Indeed.
그래
For a righteous man like yourself to act so recklessly,
항상 정직했던 사람이 이런 짓까지 하다니
you must be very lost.
너도 뭔가 두려운가 봐?
I don't know what rumors have reached your ears,
어떤 소문을 듣고 이러는지 모르겠지만
but is this really how you want to end it?
이게 네가 하려던 거야?
I only seek the truth.
난 그저 사실을 알고 싶을 뿐이야
That's all I ask.
오로지 그것뿐이라고
Come on.
젠장
Fighting my own friends
파트너에게 칼을 겨누는 거…
really sucks.
딱 질색이라고
What happened to Nagi?
나기가 대체 왜 저러는 건데
I don't know.
나도 몰라
He was acting weird before we got here.
어쩐지 이곳에 오기 전부터 이상했어
He seemed to think...
아마도…
Naomi was killed in action.
나오미가 싸우다 죽은 줄 아나 봐
Nagi, you saw it with your own eyes.
나기, 그날 너도 봤잖아
How could you say
아직도 나오미가
Naomi died in that battle?
싸우다 죽었다고 생각해?
Naomi...
나오미는…
is gone.
죽었어
Naomi was turned into an Other.
나오미는 괴이로 변한 거야
It can't be helped.
어쩔 수 없지 뭐
I must exterminate it.
처리해버릴 수밖에
No, Nagi!
나기, 얼른 멈춰
What was that?
어떻게 된 거야?
Yuito! Kasane!
유이토, 카사네
Captain Seto...
세토 대장님
Are you hurt?
괜찮아?
-No. -Good.
-네 -좋아
"ANOMALY DETECTED" His power is spiking.
(이상상태) 나기 뇌능력이 이상하게 증가하고 있어
Nagi...
나기… 너…
Don't give me that look.
왜 그런 표징이시죠?
I won't allow it.
넌 공격할 수 없어
You will spend your life in regret if you kill Yuito.
유이토를 죽이면 너는 평생 후회할 거다
Stop!
멈춰
No...
설마
I can't...
안돼…
I can't die just yet
난 아직… 죽으면 안 돼
Nagi, you're my subordinate too.
나기, 너도… 내 부하다
I will not let you go...
난 널… 보낼 수 없어
Nagi...
나기
Captain Seto...
세토 대장님
Do not let go.
손 놓지 마…
Do not let go of the Red Strings.
레드 스트링스 풀지 마
What is this?
이게 뭐야
Brother, what is happening now?
오빠, 어떻게 된 거야?
I have no clue either.
나도 모르겠어
This is unprecedented.
한 번도 이런 적 없었는데
What's wrong?
뭐지?
Kasane, what's the matter?
카사네, 왜 그래?
What is this sensation?
느낌이 이상해
What is that?
저게 뭐지…
What's happening?
뭐야?
Help!
살려주세요
Yuito, run!
유이토, 얼른 도망가
Where did Yuito go?
유이토가 사라졌어
Let's leave, it's too dangerous out here.
얼른 가, 위험해
Yuito, Kasane!
유이토, 카사네
-Save me, Major General! -Major General!
-살려주세요, 연대장님… -연대장님…
It's finally here.
드디어 나타났군
Seto!
세토
Gemma!
겜마
We're safe now, Lieutenant Colonel.
살았어, 중좌
Hang in there!
꼭 잡아
Seto...
세토…
Seto, sorry...
세토… 미안해
Are we saved?
우리… 살아남은 거야?
I wish I could say so, but...
그렇다고 말하고 싶지만…
Where is Captain Seto?
세토 대장님은?
He was taken.
삼켜버렸어
So Yuito and Kasane are...
그럼 유이토랑 카사네도…
Where am I?
뭐야?
Kasane!
카사네
Are you hurt?
괜찮아?
This doesn't feel right.
별로
Where is this place?
여기는… 어디지?
Who is that?
저건 누구야?
I don't know.
몰라
But judging by the crest,
가슴팍에 있는 배지를 보면
it's from the Sumeragi family.
스메라기 가문 사람이야
It seems like Yakumo Sumeragi.
게다가 야쿠모 스메라기인 것 같은데
I saw this in a dream.
꿈에서… 봤었어…
Kasane!
카사네
Yuito! You're finally awake.
유이토, 깨어나서 다행이야
I thought you were taken too.
그 물체가 널 삼켜버려서
I was so worried.
엄청 걱정했잖아
Where are Kasane and Nagi?
카사네는? 나기는?
We don't know.
몰라
No.
안돼
You can't do anything to help them now.
가봤자 소용없어
Had Luka not saved us just now,
루카가 없었더라면
we would have been taken too.
우리는 지금 죽었을지도 몰라
Luka?
루카?
He went looking for Major General Karen.
카렌 연대장님 찾으러 간다면서 바로 떠났어
I'm glad you're safe, Yuito.
유이토, 괜찮아서 다행이다
Gemma isn't our enemy.
겜마는 이제 적이 아니야
Right?
맞지?
I made a grave mistake.
내가 큰 잘못을 저질렀어
Gemma!
겜마
Let's check out this store when the alert is over.
경보 알림이 해제되면 여기 가볼까?
This place looks nice.
좋은데?
And the operation hour is...
영업시간이…
What happened?
뭐지?
-We can't connect to the network. -No way.
-인터넷이 안 돼 -뭐야?
-How did this happen? -What caused this?
-이거 왜 이래? -무슨 일이야?
Thankfully, my house is near a shelter.
우리 집 피난처가 부근에 있어서 다행이야
It's done.
이제 됐어
You seem to have done this a lot.
처치에 굉장히 능숙하네
I was very weak when I was a kid.
어릴 때 몸이 허약해서
I often fell sick.
자주 아팠거든
I treated my own injuries.
상처 나면 나 혼자 처치하곤 했어
You're amazing. I couldn't even do that.
짱이네, 난 할 줄 몰라
Although my uncle is the Chairman of OSF Hospital
삼촌이 토벌군병원 이사장인데도 말이야
You have a mild fever. Take these pills.
열이 좀 있어서 이거 먹으면 열 내릴 거야
Thank you.
고마워
I don't understand.
이해가 안 돼
How could you talk to him as if nothing had happened?
어떻게 저런 사람이랑 아무렇지 않게 대화할 수 있어?
Tsugumi...
츠구미
I can't forgive Gemma.
난 겜마가 용서 안 돼
Captain Seto died
세토 대장님이 죽은 건
because of Gemma's fault.
겜마가 대장님에게 부담을 안겨줬기 때문이야
Tsugumi is right.
츠구미 말이 맞아
Please tell us the whole story.
대체 무슨 일이 있었던 건지 알려줘
The New Himuka Government
뉴히무카 정부가
used Suoh Capital as a center
스오를 중심으로
to conduct social management.
사회 관리 기능을 구축하고 있어
Social management?
사회 관리?
Using physical exam as a front,
전국적인 건강검진이란 핑계로
the government finds those with power.
정부에서 초뇌능력자를 찾는 건데
Once they were recruited into OSF,
일단 토벌군에 선택되면
"COMPATIBLE" there would be no way for them to say refuse it.
(적합) 거절할 수 없게 돼
Once you're in the force, your growth will be suppressed to maintain your power.
입대 후에는 뇌능력을 유지하기 위해 신체의 성장을 억제할 거고
Everyone knows that.
그건 모두가 아는 얘기잖아
Indeed.
맞아
I know they employed this method so we could defeat the Others.
전부 괴이를 처리하기 위함이라고 했지
But there is more to that.
하지만 그게 전부가 아니었어
Do you know about the rehabilitation?
인격 교정에 관한 얘기 들어봤어?
I once had a friend
내 파트너 중 한 명이
who changed into a completely different person.
어느 날 갑자기 다른 사람이 되어버렸더라고
He used to criticize the system.
원래는 비판적인 성향이었던 친구였어
So everyone started saying
그래서 모두가
he had undergone the rehabilitation.
그 친구가 교정되었다고 판단했어
How could that happen?
어떻게 그런 일이
You are new, so you didn't know about the stories.
너희가 들어온 시간이 짧아서 모를 수도 있는데
However, it has happened many times.
이런 일이 빈번히 일어났었어
Rehabilitation is basically an open secret that we all know.
인격 교정은 이미 토벌군에서 다들 알고 있는 비밀이야
Tsugumi, you heard about it too.
츠구미, 너도 들어본 적 있지?
The government was undoubtedly behind all that.
그리고 이건 정부에서 주도한 거야
Judging by Nagi's behavior, they must have done it to him too.
아까 나기가 보인 모습도 분명 그 이유일 거야
No way...
그럴 리가
My actual age is 54 years old.
난 실제 54살이야
Soon enough, the growth suppression will wear off.
곧 있으면 성장 억제 효과도 약해질 거고
My body will age, and my power will become weak.
신체도 쇠퇴해지고 초뇌능력도 약해질 거야
Then I will have no choice but to retire.
그럼 토벌군을 떠나야 해
But before that,
그래서 그전에
I hope to learn the truth.
진실을 확인하고 싶었던 거야
That's when Karen told me
그때 카렌이 그러더라
that Seto had taken part in the rehabilitation.
세토가 인격 교정 연구에 참여했다고
Captain Seto would never do such a thing.
세토 대장님은 그런 사람이 아니야
Indeed. Why didn't I believe him?
그러게, 내가 왜 못 믿었던 걸까?
I'm so sorry.
진짜 너무 미안해…
Does that mean Major General Karen
그럼 카렌 연대장님이
is against New Himuka's method?
뉴히무카 정부의 방식을 반대하는 거야?
No.
아니…
It's finally here.
드디어 나타났군
There seems to be some inside story to it.
뭔가 내막이 있는 것 같아
Karen's true plan...
카렌의 진짜 속셈에
must be something else.
그 사람도 있을 거야
Chief Sumeragi!
스메라기 본부장님
A large number of Others are invading central Suoh Capital!
괴이가 대량으로 스오 중앙부에 침입했습니다
What?
뭐?
Eradicate them immediately.
얼른 처리해
But our defense system is not working.
하지만 방어 시스템이 전혀 작동하지 않고
Psynet is offline as well.
사이넷도 끊겼습니다
What about the council?
평의회 쪽은?
We don't know.
그쪽도…
We couldn't contact them.
연락이 안 됩니다
Could it be that Arahabaki...
설마… 아라하바키가…
Karen, how did it turn out this way?
카렌이 왜 이렇게 변한 거지?
I will retrieve it this time.
이번에는 반드시 되찾을 거다
Kasane?
카사네…
Was that a dream?
그거… 꿈인 건가…
Are you all right?
괜찮아?
I'm all right.
응
Where are we?
여기는…
Kasane, look at that.
카사네, 저쪽 봐봐
That's Kunad Highway.
여기는 쿠나도 고속도로잖아
What happened?
무슨 일이 있었던 거야?
We don't know either.
우리도 잘 몰라
This is what we see when we woke up.
깨어보니 이렇게 되었더라고
Hurry up, Kasane.
어서 와, 카사네
♪I don't need to let fate dictate me♪
운명의 지시 따윈 필요 없어
♪Because I believe that I can rewrite it♪
분명 고쳐질 거라 믿으니까
♪I'll always be a dreamer now and forever♪
앞으로도 꿈을 꿀 수 있게 말이야
♪Another sunrise shines now and it blacks out♪
눈부시게 빛나는 태양이 막을 내리고
♪What's waiting for us at the world's end♪
세상의 끝에서 뭘 기다리고 있는걸까
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going♪
미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
♪Who can shake us♪
누가 우리를 위협해
♪Who can define us♪
누가 우리 대신 결정해
♪It's nothing less than our story♪
이건 우리만의 스토리야
♪Forever eternal, keep the fire going in your heart♪
네 마음속 미래의 불빛은 영원히 꺼지지 않아
KAREN'S BETRAYAL
(카렌의 반란)